Hello, I'm going to introduce you to the
EBati CartoAmiante platform, renowned
EBatiSoft,
that I have had the opportunity to develop
during my permanent contract at
Soft Concept
in pairs. As a reminder,
is a Lyon-based software publisher
Specialized in investigations of everything
Media Type: Mobile, Tablet and
computer. The project lasted about a year
and was done
in
collaboration with
the company Chevalier Diag,
which is a company specializing in the
diagnosis
technical expertise in various
areas, including real estate,
construction and the environment. And a
holding company specialising in real estate,
Akinext. The software, for the
Objective of following the regulations
asbestos
and the identification of precautions
special needs to be taken in the event of work
on buildings. He is at his destination
of landlords and property managers
real estate companies, co-ownership trustees,
hotel rooms, etc. The
platform was made in HTML, CSS,
Javascript, in C#
for the back-end and with the tools
specific to Soft Concept that
are Net-Survey, Ethnos
and Web Reports. Net-Survey for
creation of questionnaires, Ethnos for
data analysis, for
power
have stats like
for example here. For
Credit by
example
the percentage of buildings with asbestos
known, the
Different category distributions
functions of each vessel, the
number of customers, etc. and Web Reports
that allows you to design applications
with less code. The objective
secondary school
The platform is
Of course to dematerialize as much as possible
possible wealth management,
particularly in connection with risk monitoring
asbestos within a
real estate stock. Must
in
enables compliance with obligations
DTA surveillance files, i.e.
asbestos techniques and the various
periodic assessments to prepare for the
securing a construction site. In fact
Each building requires management
all the more complex as the evolutions
regulatory changes will be frequent.
So the objective is to digitize on the
PDF format of the teaching files
papers. So by
example
a vessel may
belong to a
area or a theme, so joinery
infrastructure, infrastructure,
railings, et cetera. A location,
in the application, can
have several buildings and in
each building, we have several
equipment. We can do audits and
we can have
Deadlines. So the deadlines, it's going to be
work after an audit that may be
periodical or not, continued by
example to a
Asbestos overview that does not comply with
not the
regulations and which imposes a
intervention. Quite urgent therefore
The application can therefore have access
statistics as I
I showed just now. We can
also manage
these settlements. So, for example,
one
can go inside a
location, select to be able to
to go inside and have
the different buildings. We can filter
by address, postcode, city
or category.
So there, for example,
We have 3 locations with a building
in each of them. We can
also have a cartographic vision
of the various buildings.
So there, for example,
If we zoom in here, we're going to be able to
have the Marguerite brewery,
so the building automatically. The
attached building, it is the Brasserie la
brewery
Marguerite who,
by the way, is a very
good address in Lyon. I
advise you so here are 2 visions,
a vision with the leaflet, the Google
Maps and
The Vision
with the different
establishments, therefore, knowing that
The platform administrator can
show what's visible for. The
customer so there for example, we have there
for example, the themes that
are grayed out, the themes are not
audits. neither. According to
the role of the user, the person
who uses the app, there will be
Have shares
that will be possible. Of course.
So now, we
goes
therefore take an interest in the
Audits.
So, in fact, audits are fine
to finally manage everything that
will be an asbestos technical file.
Therefore
if the work is to be carried out at the
within the building, we will be able to recover
all the analyses that will be
necessary at the beginning of the work. So the
under the name of the location, the theme,
the State. So, for example, here we will have
different states for asbestos.
So there, for example, the building is
dilapidation. The cause, the
As a result, it's going to be wear and tear
normal in the time of the work.
The
next deadline, the work to be carried out
realize, are they going to be
urgent or not? So there, among other things,
they are not urgent and we will
for example to be able to
Import images to illustrate
auditing. There are audits of course,
completed, audits to be carried out
In the future, we can always filter.
By location, et cetera as well
also the work, because in fact we have
a location, a building,
we have areas and themes such as
saw it just now with the little ones
icons, and we also have a book. We can
filter by equipment status.
So it's not just dilapidated, it's
several, but in the 7 examples, it is
That's all there is to it. And the urgency, is it
the work is urgent or
not urgent? Do the
Are the work done or not? So the
Deadlines. The deadlines will be the
Controls
asbestos that
Will
soon to arrive, who
arrive within 3 months. So there is
different types of maturities. There are the
corrective actions and evaluations
Periodicals. Periodic evaluations,
As the name suggests, they are
evaluations that will be made
regularly, so we'll be able to
classify according to coming or exceeding. And the
corrective actions, it will be in particular
deterioration. By
Compared to a previous intervention
so it's going to be filed in this section
there. Well so the DTAs, it's going to be
Technical files
asbestos, so the PDFs that go as a result
be imported into the application, which
will respect a certain format and
so all the information
will meet here and we
will be able to find out if there are any
asbestos or not on the report that will have
been done. So the objective
In fact, it's on existing reports
and on the new PDFs, to be able to
Integrate directly into the platform
and have access to all the
information quickly and at the same time
place. The objective is also to
centralize information and
Automate reporting. So we don't
more have
paper files,
but to have
Files
in PDF format. And of the
to improve knowledge too
of the patrimony to be able to
so geolocate the
Asbestos risk within the building stock
and to have a more global vision of the
problem, to know what type of
category is more impacted by another,
and so forth. So there the statistics, we
will find the same statistics here,
so there it is
a global follow-up.